sixshot.com 2006-11-11

# TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE :: Hip-Hop Review

|  | 

REVIEWS 

|   
---|---  

Article by: [bab](http://community.sixshot.com/bab)

This site is a database of information of Hip-Hop related content. While every effort has been made to ensure the accuracy of the displayed information, Sixshot GmbH gives no warranty as to the accuracy of contained information. **Use of Information:** As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to the Site. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Sixshot Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience in our sites. 

The various registration forms and surveys may request that you give us contact information (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address) demographic information (such as your age and gender) and profile data (such as your preferences in entertainment). Information submitted at the time of registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Sixshot GmbH, and may be shared with our promotional partners. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties. With your permission, we may use your contact information to send you information about our companies and what we're doing. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Choice/Opt-out section below.   
  
**Use of Materials Located on This Site:** This site is owned and/or operated by Sixshot GmbH ("Owner"). No material from this site or any Web site owned, operated, licensed, or controlled by Owner may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, except that you may download one copy of the materials on any single computer for your personal, noncommercial home use, provided you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices.

Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of the Owner copyrights and other proprietary rights. The use of any such material on any other Web site or networked computer environment is prohibited. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names are proprietary to Owner or the other designated owner of a posted mark.

Elements of Owner sites are protected by trade dress and other laws and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part. No logo, graphic, sound or image from any Owner site may be copied or retransmitted unless expressly permitted by Owner.

 **Media Files:** All media streams featured at Sixshot GmbH are provided from the corresponding owners or record companies for promotional usage. Sixshot GmbH does not host or reproduce any media files. Therefore the copyrights to the media belongs to the Media's owner and not to Sixshot GmbH.

**Public Forums:** This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in such public forums will immediately become public information and you should restrict your disclosure of personal information to any information that you are willing to have available to the public. 

**Use of IP Addresses:** An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you're surfing the Web. When you request pages from Sixshot GmbH, our servers log your IP address. Sixshot GmbH collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our Sites. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you will be anonymous to us. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, or others.

 **Links to Other Sites:** Sixshot GmbH is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may also be linked to websites operated by other companies. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site's respective privacy policies and practices.  
 **  
Choice/Opt-Out:** Our Sites may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list to not receive future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, it is best to follow the specific instructions outlined within the communications you receive from us. However, if you are unable to complete the process indicated in the communications, then just send  an e-mail to [mailing@sixshot.ch](mailto:mailing@sixshot.ch) with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject to be removed from our communications.

 **Special Note for Parents:** If you have concerns about this site or its services, wish to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our services, or wish to cancel your child's membership, please contact us at [info@Sixshot GmbH](mailto:myinfo@alloy.com). Our site will not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under 13 years old in violation of applicable laws. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to our site without your permission, you may contact us at [info@Sixshot GmbH](mailto:myinfo@alloy.com). We have taken commercially reasonable steps to restrict use of this site to those who are at least 13 years old. We do not sell products for purchase by children and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only, or with adult permission.  
 **  
Your Acceptance of These Terms:** By using Sixshot GmbH, you signify your acceptance of this Sixshot GmbH Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. Sixshot GmbH reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of Sixshot GmbH following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Last updated June 28th, 2004

Peep the [ **review archive**](http://www.sixshot.com/section.asp?id=3)

**Send** this Story [**to a Friend**](http://www.sixshot.com/mailto.asp?id=912)

| **2 Comments on this article** | [Leave your comment](http://www.sixshot.com/comment_leave.asp?id=912)  
---|---  
  
From : [_dj socker_](http://community.sixshot.com/dj%20socker)  
**aigh**  
aigh  
  
From : [_FeVaBlistaZ_](http://community.sixshot.com/FeVaBlistaZ)  
**ight**  
ight  

© 1997-2006 by Sixshot GmbH, all rights reserved  
Best view with IE 4.0 or higher
